<resources>
    <string name="demo_app_name">Carrier App</string>
    <string name="buy_now">Buy Now</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart">Add To Cart</string>
    <string name="no_stock">No Stock</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait</string>
    <string name="app_title">E-Commerce Demo App</string>
    <string name="info_txt">Press Back button once logged in from user registration.</string>
    <string name="register">Login</string>
    <string name="activity">Launch as Fragment</string>
    <string name="adding_to_cart">Adding To Cart</string>
    <string name="loading_cart">Loading Cart</string>
    <string name="select_country">Select Country</string>
    <string name="select_env">Select Environment</string>
    <string name="shop_now">Shop Now</string>
    <string name="order_history">Order History</string>
    <string name="launch_product_detail">Launch Product Detail</string>
    <string name="iap_unknown_error">Unknown Error</string>
    <string name="iap_no_connection">No Connection, Connect to network and try again.</string>
    <string name="iap_connection_timeout">Connection Timeout</string>
    <string name="iap_auth_failure">Authentication Failure</string>
    <string name="iap_prod_out_of_stock">Products out of stock</string>
    <string name="categorized_shop_now">Shop Now(Categorized)</string>
    <string name="categorized_shop_now_ignore_retailer">Shop With Ignored Retailer "%s"</string>
    <string name="buy_direct">Buy Direct</string>
    //Theme Settings
    <string name="page_title_theme_settings">Theme Setting</string>
    <string name="tonal_range_label">Content tonal range</string>
    <string name="for_content_area_text">For Contents Area</string>
    <string name="for_navigation_area_text">For Navigation Area</string>
    <string name="accent_color_range_text">Accent color range</string>
    <string name="content_desc_close">close</string>
    <string name="color_ranges_label">Color range</string>
    <string name="warning_text">This color is not selectable with current theme combination. Please re-select alternatives above to use this color.</string>
    <string name="set_theme_settings">Set</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>

    <string name="personalConsentAcceptanceText">Information on Collection and Use of Personal Information
        [Purpose of collecting and using personal information]end. Performance of contracts regarding the provision of services;
        -Content provision, specific custom service provision, identity verification
        I. Membership Management
        -Identity verification using the membership system and limited identity verification system
        -Prevention of illegal use by unauthorized members and prevention of unauthorized use
        -Confirmation of subscription intention, restriction of subscription
        [Items collected for personal information]
        -Required items: name, date of birth, gender, email address, password
        -Optional items: address, phone number
        [Retention and Use Period of Personal Information]
        In principle, personal information of the information subject is destroyed without delay when the purpose of collecting and using personal information is achieved. However, the following information will be retained for the period specified for the reasons below.
        end. Reasons for information retention by company internal policy
        -Fraudulent records
        Reason for retention: Prevention of fraudulent use
        Retention period: 5 years
        I. Reasons for information retention pursuant to related laws
        -If it is necessary to preserve according to the provisions of related laws such as the Act on the Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce, etc., the member information will be kept for a certain period of time.
        -Records on contract or withdrawal of subscription
        Reason for retention: Act on Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce, etc.
        Retention period: 5 years
        Records of consumer complaints or disputes
        Reason for retention: Act on Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce, etc.
        Retention period: 3 years
[Right of refusing consent to collect personal information]
You may not agree to the collection and use of such personal information. Online consultations are still available if you decline to agree, but your Philips membership service will be limited (but you will not be able to sign up if you do not enter the required information, which is the minimum required for membership).For more details about the collection and use of personal information of the company, please click the URL below.
       <a href="http://www.philips.com">http://www.philips.co.kr/privacypolicy_online</a>  </string>
    <string name="personalConsentAcceptanceText_Error">Please accept the Personal Consent</string>
    <string name="personalConsentText">I accept the Personal Consent</string>
</resources>
